{
    "subject": "resource/When_We_Were_Twenty-One",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributor",
    "object": "resource/Paramount_Pictures",
    "human_readable": "When We Were Twenty-One was distributed by Paramount Pictures.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7154207229614258,
            "question": "Who distributed the film 'When We Were Twenty-One'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6875559687614441,
            "question": "Is 'When We Were Twenty-One' a film distributed by a major studio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5716744661331177,
            "question": "What year was 'When We Were Twenty-One' likely released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5467171669006348,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that was distributed by Paramount Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4564243257045746,
            "question": "Name a film distributed by Paramount Pictures."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4146909713745117,
            "question": "Which company released the movie 'When We Were Twenty-One'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3726915419101715,
            "question": "What kind of company is Paramount Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35470718145370483,
            "question": "Can you think of other films with similar themes to 'When We Were Twenty-One'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3254861831665039,
            "question": "Give an example of another film distributed by Paramount Pictures."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.030027110129594803,
            "question": "What is the role of a film distributor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When We Were Twenty-One was distributed by Paramount Pictures.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3084_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of another film distributed by Paramount Pictures.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3084_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of other films with similar themes to 'When We Were Twenty-One'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3084_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of company is Paramount Pictures?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3084_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_157.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3084_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer to the query is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}\n\nExplanation:\nThe context information mentions that \"When We Were Twenty-One\" is a film directed by Hugh Ford and Edwin S. Porter, and it was released on April 5, 1915, by Paramount Pictures. Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that When We Were Twenty-One was distributed by Paramount Pictures."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the film \"When We Were Twenty-One\" was distributed by Paramount Pictures, which aligns with the provided query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}